<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Town Crier</title>
    <description>HearYe is an iOS app that allows students to find things to do on campus, http://www.hearye.io
</description>
    <link>http://www.blog.hearye.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.blog.hearye.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 20:36:57 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 20:36:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Never Underestimate the Power of Free Things</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://dailynorthwestern.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/DannyBrown3-KaiHuang-1024x678.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Dillo Day 2016&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every year Northwestern hosts the nation’s largest student-run music festival called “Dillo Day”. Founded in 1972, it takes place on the ‘lakefill’ area of campus, sitting right on Lake Michigan. To get onto the lakefill however, the students have to funnel through a checkpoint; we knew that this bottleneck was a perfect opportunity to promote HearYe. The logistical planning for our Dillo Day marketing campaign had been our minds several weeks prior to the event, but truly began once we convinced ourselves that it was a good idea to market without a product. After several debates about the possibility of marketing an idea without a product people can download and interact with, we settled on an idea: pass out customized bags with informational fliers inside. We also put a water bottle in each bag, as we knew that would be a major selling point (more on that later).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We bought 150 bags to distribute on Dillo Day, as well as a banner to place on the plastic folding table we borrowed from some friends. Because of the nature of Dillo Day, we thought we would not be able to obtain permits to set up a table “officially”. So, we just decided to pitch a table and give away bags until we were kicked out. With the event three days away, the planning was done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://files.slack.com/files-pri/T0J7L8Y14-F1D5PL0RF/pasted_image_at_2016_05_31_08_35_pm.png&quot; alt=&quot;Hearye Bag&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We woke up early on May 21st, packed the bags with fliers, stickers, and water before enjoying some of the morning’s tailgating festivities (shouts out to some groups for free food). We met at Max’s house at 1:30–where the bags, banners, and table were–and hauled the goods over to Sheridan and Foster. We set up the table faster than a NASCAR team changes wheels during a pit, and before we knew it, we were swarmed by people asking for bags. More importantly, however, was the fact that people were asking us about our product and what it was about. When we gave them the pitch, we knew they wanted it. The bags flew off the table, and in just 15 minutes we had given away all 150 of them. We dropped the table and banner of at Max’s house, then went to the lakefill to enjoy the annual music festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, Dillo Day proved to be a fantastic day, and one of many small successes. The demand for HearYe was figuratively shown by the amount of people asking about what the product is about, and literally shown by the amount of orange bags seen walking around the lakefill. We also experienced a greater number of unique hits on our website throughout the following days, and saw increased interaction around the site as well. Additionally, we thought that we would be giving away bags for an hour and a half–not 15 minutes. The demand for the bags, and much more importantly, our product, was underestimated by our whole team. This validated the idea behind HearYe, and motivates us to build the best product possible in the coming months. Never underestimate the power of free materials to get people excited about your product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;– Drake&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 09:31:12 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.blog.hearye.io/updates/2016/05/31/dilloday.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.blog.hearye.io/updates/2016/05/31/dilloday.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>updates</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>HearYe Update 2</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;•	The HearYe Partnership Program with groups is now under way! We are proud to partner with Northwestern student groups and are excited that they are early adopters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•	HearYe has begun integrating Amazon Web Services Lambda which expedites the request and response process and functions independently from a server, which will allow HearYe to take many requests without being overloaded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•	A secure log-in system has now been integrated, and the event display feed is now in development!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•	Lastly, new marketing materials arrived! We have some awesome stickers, and look for us on &lt;a href=&quot;http://dilloday.com&quot;&gt;Dillo Day&lt;/a&gt; for surprise HearYe gear and swag!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;– Max, Co-founder&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 09:39:22 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.blog.hearye.io/updates/2016/05/10/update2.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.blog.hearye.io/updates/2016/05/10/update2.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>updates</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Your Organization Needs to be on Slack</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When connecting with coworkers, clients, and others, email has been the go-to medium.Email provided solutions to the problems of traditional “snail” mail. It was faster and cheaper, people could send attachments and forward messages to people. But as technology has changed, the user experience of emails for work teams has not. As HearYe found out, it involves a clunky process of providing different subjects, and adding recipients with each email, and if a thread of emails ensues, it can be difficult to navigate through all of the replies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://files.slack.com/files-pri/T0J7L8Y14-F17PZR7NX/slack_photo.png&quot; alt=&quot;HearYe on Slack&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As email was to traditional mail, Slack is to email. To fix all of the clutter that the email platform suffers from in work group communication, Slack allows communities, groups or teams join a “channel” through a URL or email invitation sent by the channel admin. These channels allow team members to communicate in real time, and in a more organic way similar to texting. However, in the channel files can be posted and are immediately shared to all members and can be interact with and previewed inside of Slack. If you want to break the large group up into smaller ones, sub-channels can be created for these smaller groups and private direct messaging is also available to all members in the channel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using different channels for different projects, but still maintaining a general channel allows groups to break up and focus on certain tasks whilst also being able to communicate to the full team. HearYe implemented slack back in February of this year, and it completely changed team communication and collaboration. Prior to Slack, our team was using Facebook Messenger, and that quickly became cluttered with different topic threads and files. After switching to Slack, team communication became much more organized, task management more transparent, file sharing more expedient, and project execution more precise. As a team, we have yet to even see the full potential of Slack, but we know that the more we use it, the more productive we will be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a business or an organization, it’s time to leave email behind when it comes to project management and communication. Email chains get so cluttered that you spend more time digging through your inbox trying to find the right email instead of using that time to work on the project you came to complete. Slack’s simple interface and multitude of features ensures that you will be on top of your game when communicating and working with your coworkers and group mates. Slack is the way is the way of the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a postscript, our team believes in the future of Slack so much, that they created their own task manager application for Slack called Octopus!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;– Max, Co-founder&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 09:25:22 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.blog.hearye.io/articles/2016/05/10/slack.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.blog.hearye.io/articles/2016/05/10/slack.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>articles</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>hearye, hearye</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;…And we’re live! Now that the website is up, the countdown begins for the release of app. Until then, we will be releasing updates and insight about the process as we go along. For this blog, we will give a little history about HearYe and its founders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It all started one Friday night when both Drake and I were trying to figure out what to do for the evening. We knew that there were events happening around Northwestern, from political speaking events to movie screenings. However, the only resources that we knew of to find more information about the events were by trying to find flyers around campus or trying to search through Facebook events that were sparsely available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that evening, an idea was born. Why not just create a platform where every individual and group on campus can post their events and where anyone on campus can see them on their iPhone? So that is what we have set out to do at HearYe. Once we Drake and I nailed down that this is what we wanted to do, we added Brandon, Navin, and John to our team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking forward to the future of HearYe!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;– Max, Co-founder&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 11:51:22 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.blog.hearye.io/updates/2016/03/09/initial-commit.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.blog.hearye.io/updates/2016/03/09/initial-commit.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>updates</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
